If you look around the streets of London, you’ll see the many methods people use to move around.
环顾伦敦的街头，你会看到人们出行的方式五花八门。
Whether it’s on a commute to work, a trip to the shops, or a sightseeing excursion, there are people on buses, the Tube, cars, motorbikes, bicycles and even roller skates.
无论是通勤上班、购物出行还是观光游览，都能看到人们乘坐公交车、地铁、汽车、摩托车、自行车，甚至踩着旱冰鞋出行。
The roads are already congested; and now there’s a new addition: electric, or 'e-scooters'.
伦敦的道路本就十分拥堵，如今又多了一种新的交通工具：电动滑板车。
This traditional children’s vehicle has become more sophisticated over the years.
这款原本是儿童玩具的交通工具，这些年变得越发精密复杂。
And now, with the addition of a small electric motor, it’s become a cheap and easy mode of transport.
如今，它加装了小型电动机，成了一种经济便捷的出行方式。
Scooting around town can be fun and doesn’t involve much effort, so it’s no wonder they’re becoming increasingly popular in cities around the world.
骑着它在城市里穿梭既有趣又省力，难怪它在全球各大城市越来越受欢迎。
But following what’s believed to be the first fatal accident involving an electric scooter in the UK, questions are being asked about their safety and whether traffic laws should be changed.
但在英国发生了首例疑似涉及电动滑板车的致命事故后，人们开始质疑其安全性，以及是否应该修改交通法规。
Some scooter riders have been seen on pavements; others on the road jumping red traffic lights, adding to the frustration of motorists stuck in jams.
有人看到一些滑板车骑手在人行道上行驶，还有一些骑手在马路上闯红灯，这让堵在车流中的司机们愈发烦躁。
In the UK, the law states that riding one on the public highway or pavement is forbidden.
英国法律规定，禁止在公共公路或人行道上骑行电动滑板车。
Riders currently face a £300 fixed-penalty notice and six points on their driving licence for doing so.
目前，违规骑行者会收到300英镑的定额罚款通知，驾照还会被扣6分。
But, despite this, it seems the increasing popularity of e-scooters means they can be seen everywhere.
但即便如此，电动滑板车的热度依旧不减，大街小巷随处可见。
And now users are calling on regulations to be changed.
如今，滑板车用户纷纷呼吁修改相关法规。
The UK government is looking at how safely they can be used on the road and is ‘reviewing’ the law.
英国政府正在研究电动滑板车如何才能安全上路，并对相关法律进行“审查”。
But its transport minister, Michael Ellis, has told the BBC that: "Micromobility products are appearing in countries across the globe and are an exciting innovation for which we know there is demand.
不过，英国交通大臣迈克尔·埃利斯向英国广播公司表示：“微移动产品是一项令人激动的创新，正在全球各国普及，我们也知道市场对其存在需求。
However, safety must always be our top priority when considering their use on public highways in this country.”
但在考虑这类产品在本国公共道路上的使用问题时，安全必须始终是我们的首要考量。”
There’s no doubt there are dangers in riding a two-wheeled scooter.
毫无疑问，骑两轮滑板车存在不少安全隐患。
Despite the fact that some of them can exceed 30mph, they sometimes only have one brake and no lights.
尽管有些电动滑板车的时速能超过30英里，但它们往往只有一个刹车，而且没有车灯。
They also become unstable if the rider hits a pothole, and however confident the rider may be, larger vehicles on the road make them vulnerable.
骑手一旦碾过路面的坑洼，车身就会变得不稳。此外，无论骑手有多自信，马路上体型更大的车辆都会让他们处于弱势地位。
So it seems more work needs to be done to give e-scooters a safe and legal space to travel in.
因此，要为电动滑板车开辟安全合法的出行空间，显然还有很多工作要做。